Matej Hric

Junior developer

Contact Details

J +421 950 392 490

→ hricmatej9@gmail.com

🚱 , Slovakia

+ Driving licence B

Core Skills

- Software & tools
- Flexibility
- Organisation
- Planning

Professional Profile

As an enthusiastic and innovative junior software developer with specific experience in C# and .NET framework, including working with WinForms and PostgreSQL database. I possess a deep technical knowledge across IT systems including hardware, software, networking, and security, alongside confidently delivering support solutions that ensure optimal levels of IT.My aim is to further develop my professional knowledge and technical skills by studying Software Engineering at SDU in Denmark, where I anticipate that my passion for technology and commitment to software development will contribute to my academic and professional growth.

Education

• **Diploma** | Gymnázium dukliankych hrdinov | Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

Career Summary

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022 Gazelle, Netherlands

Product Assembly Team Member

Outline

I actively participated in the assembly of high-quality bicycles in a fast and dynamic production environment.

Jan 2023 - Jul 2023 PEHAcom, Slovakia Junior software developer

Outline

I designed and developed software applications for doctors, aimed at improving their daily work processes and increasing efficiency in processing patient data.

Additional

Hobbies & Interests

Chess, Cooking, Travel

Software

Microsoft office, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Microsoft Teams

Hardware

Desktops, Printers, Routers, Telephony

Programming Languages

C# /. NET, PostgresSQL, HTML/CSS, TypeScript, Git/GitHub

Languages

Slovak (Native), English (Upper-intermediate), Russian (Elementary), Japanese (Beginner)